Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 9: Boxes 507-571
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 9: Boxes 507-571
- United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, Publication (Box 529, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Too many hours - Comic book about the struggle for the 8 hour work day, Publication (Box 529, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Foreign competition: made in the U.S.A., 1984; Publication (Box 529, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Foreign competition: made in the U.S.A., 1984; Publication (Box 529, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Basic principles: aggressive struggle, rank and file control, 1983; Publication (Box 529, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Basic principles: aggressive struggle, rank and file control, 1983; Publication (Box 529, Folder 1)
- United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, Publication (Box 529, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Constitution and by-laws - Dec. 1, 1989, Publication (Box 529, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Agreement and pension and insurance agreement between Westinghouse Electric Corporation and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers (A.F.L.-C.I.O.-C.L.C.): July 12, 1982, Publication (Box 529, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Agreement and pension and insurance agreement between Westinghouse Electric Corporation and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers (A.F.L.-C.I.O.-C.L.C.): July 12, 1982, Publication (Box 529, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Agreement and pension and insurance agreement between Westinghouse Electric Corporation and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers (A.F.L.-C.I.O.-C.L.C.): July 16, 1979, Publication (Box 529, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Agreement and pension and insurance agreement between Westinghouse Electric Corporation and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers (A.F.L.-C.I.O.-C.L.C.): June 16, 1973, Publication (Box 529, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Agreement and pension and insurance agreement between Westinghouse Electric Corporation and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers (U.E.): July 12, 1982, Publication (Box 529, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Agreement and pension and insurance agreement between Westinghouse Electric Corporation and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers (U.E.): July 12, 1982, Publication (Box 529, Folder 2)
- United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, Publication (Box 529, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: National Agreement between General Electric Company and United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America (UE): 1982-1985 (Box 529, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: National Agreement between General Electric Company and United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America (UE): 1991-1994 (Box 529, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Agreement between Stromberg-Carlson Corporation and Local No. 338 of the International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, AFL-CIO-CLC and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, AFL-CIO-CLC: 1974-1977 (Box 529, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Agreement Local No. 324, United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America (UE) with Fairbanks Company, Binghamton, N.Y.: 1970-1973 (Box 529, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Agreement between Kennedy Valve Mfg. Co., Inc. and United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America (UE) and Local 329: June 1970, Publication (Box 529, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Agreement between GTE Sylvania Inc., Greenland, New Hampshire and United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America (UE) and its Local No. 294: June 8, 1976-August 1, 1978, 1976-1978 (Box 529, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Agreement between Emporium Plants of GTE Sylvania Incorporated and United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America (UE): September 30, 1976 to December 1, 1979, 1976-1979 (Box 529, Folder 3)
- IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), Publication (Box 529, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Agreement between Appalachian Power Company and Local Union No. 978, Logan Bargaining Unit, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers: April 1, 1974, March 31, 1976, 1974-1976 (Box 529, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Agreement between Local 827 International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO and Bell Atlantic-New Jersey, Inc. and Bell Atlantic-Network Services, Inc., Plant and Engineering Departments: Effective May 21, 1995, Publication (Box 529, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Agreement between AVX Ceramics, Olean, New York and Local Union No. 1690, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO-CLC: 1979-1982 (Box 529, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Agreement between American Telephone and Telegraph Company on behalf of certain business units and divisions and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Locals 134, 165, 188, 206, 336, 363, 383, 399, 827, 1011, 1944, 2213, 2222, 2313, 2320, 2321, 1988; Publication (Box 529, Folder 4)
- IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), Publication (Box 529, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Agreement between Local 827 International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO and Bell Atlantic-New Jersey, Inc. and Bell Atlantic-Network Services, Inc., Plant and Engineering Departments: Effective May 21, 1995, Publication (Box 529, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Agreement, Big Rivers Electric Corporation and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 1701: April 23, 1984, Publication (Box 529, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Agreement, Big Rivers Electric Corporation and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 1701: April 23, 1987, Publication (Box 529, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Agreement between Atlantic Richfield Company, Four Corners Pipe Line Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, A.F.L.-C.I.O. and C.L.C., Local union number 2295, 1988-1990 (Box 529, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Collective bargaining contract between Associated Universities, Inc., Brookhaven National Laboratory and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local Union 2230: 8-1-78 to 8-1- 79, 1978-1979 (Box 529, Folder 5)
- IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), Publication (Box 530, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Agreement between Local 827 International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO and New Jersey Bell Telephone Company: organization of Vice President and Comptroller adn General Departments: Effective August 7, 1983, Publication (Box 530, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Agreement between New England Telephone and Telegraph Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO Locals 2222, 2320, 2321, 2322, 2323, 2324, 2325, 2326, 2327: effective: August 10, 1980, Publication (Box 530, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Agreement between the New England Telephone Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (AFL-CIO) Locals 2222, 2313, 2315, 2320, 2321, 2323, 2324, 2326, 2327: effective August 10, 1980, Publication (Box 530, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Agreement between the New York Telephone Company and the NYNEX Service Company and the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 2213: effective December 4, 1989, Publication (Box 530, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Agreement between Local 827 International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO and New Jersey Bell Telephone Company: organization of Vice President and Comptroller adn General Departments: Effective August 6, 1989, Publication (Box 530, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Agreement between International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 569 and National Steel and Shipbuilding Company, 1987; Publication (Box 530, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Agreement between International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 569 and National Steel and Shipbuilding Company, 1987; Publication (Box 530, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Agreement between NYNEX Mobile Communications Company and the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO: effective January 1, 1992, Publication (Box 530, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Agreement between the New York Telephone Company and theTelesector Resources Group, Inc. and the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 2213: effective December 4, 1989, amended September 1, 1991, Publication (Box 530, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: 1982-84 Municipal coalition economic agreement, 1982-1984 (Box 530, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Agreement between Niagara Mohawk Power Corporation, and System Council, U-11, and Local Unions 1339, 1352 (Western Division), 79, 310, 478, 554, 836, 1484 (Central Division), and 137, 1369, 1371, and 1385 (Eastern Division) International Brotherhood of El, 1986; Publication (Box 530, Folder 1)
- IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), Publication (Box 530, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Agreement between Hawaiian Telephone and Local 1357, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO: 1976-1979 (Box 530, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Agreement between Reidsville Plant of GTE Sylvania Incorporated and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 2290: January 1, 1974 to December 31, 1976, 1974-1976 (Box 530, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Agreement between Ipswich Plant of G.T.E. Sylvania Incorporated and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, A.F. of L.-C.I.O., Local 1502: August 30, 1976 to October 4, 1979, 1976-1979 (Box 530, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Agreement between Equitable Gas Company and Local Union 1956 of the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1980- 1982 (Box 530, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Agreement between Ingalls Shipbuilding Division, Litton Systems, Inc., Pascagoula, Mississippi and the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local Union no. 733: September 26, 1983 -February 1, 1987, 1983-1987 (Box 530, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Labor agreement between the Hudson Pulp & Paper Corp., Palatka, Florida and the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Palatka Local 1583: June 1, 1974 to June 1, 1977, 1974-1977 (Box 530, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Labor agreement by and between International Paper Company, Vicksburg Mill and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers: September 27, 1982 through September 26, 1985, 1982-1985 (Box 530, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Agreement between Hawaiian Telephone and Local 1357, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO: 1974-1976 (Box 530, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Agreement between Imaging & Sensing Technology Corporation and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 1833-1, Horseheads, NY: May 1, 1991, Publication (Box 530, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Articles of agreement between Contel, Continental Telephone Company of New York, Inc. and Local Union 363 & 1725 of the IBEW, 1986; Publication (Box 530, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Contract between the Pacific Telephone and Telegraph Company and Bell Telephone Company of Nevada and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local Union 1269, 1980; Publication (Box 530, Folder 2)
- IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), Publication (Box 530, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Constitution and by-laws - United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, 1995; Publication (Box 530, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Agreement between Cornell University and Tompkins-Cortland Counties Building Trades Council, Maintenance Division: July 1, 1986-June 30, 1989: July 1, 1988-June 30, 1989, contract extended to June 30, 1991, 1988-1991 (Box 530, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Agreement between the Detroit Edison Co. and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 17: Signed September 17, 1974, Publication (Box 530, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Collective bargaining contract between Consolidated Edison Company of New York, Inc. (Staten Island) and the Local Union No. 3 of the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO: June 25, 1989 through June 19, 1993, Publication (Box 530, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: 1978 agreement International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO-CLC and CBS Inc., Publication (Box 530, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Agreement between Cooper Industries, Inc., Crouse-Hinds Division and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local #2084: April 1, 1990-March 31, 1993, Publication (Box 530, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Agreement between Crouse-Hinds Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local #2084: dated April 1, 1981, Publication (Box 530, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Agreement between the Detroit Edison Co. and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 17: signed September 17, 1974, Publication (Box 530, Folder 3)
- IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), Publication (Box 530, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Contract Carolina Telephone and Telegraph Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO & CLC: December 1, 1978, Publication (Box 530, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: 1978 agreement International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO-CLC and CBS Inc., Publication (Box 530, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: 1981 agreement International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO-CLC and CBS Inc., Publication (Box 530, Folder 4)
- IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), Publication (Box 531, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Settlement of 1991 negotiations: Memorandum of agreement, Publication (Box 531, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Agreement between the Mountain States Telephone and Telegraph Company, Directory Advertising Representatives, Directory Sales Representatives, Marketing Assistants-Directory, Directory Sales, Representatives-Trainee, Customer Service Representatives and I, 1980; Publication (Box 531, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Agreement between McDonnell Douglas Corporation, Douglas Aircraft Company and McDonnell Douglas Astronautics, Huntington Beach, components of McDonnell Douglas Corporation and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local No. 2295: effective date:, 1981; Publication (Box 531, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Agreement between the Mountain States Telephone and Telegraph Company and Local Union 206, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers: Recognition and Working Agreement: Effective August 10, 1980, Publication (Box 531, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Labor agreement between Minnkota Power Cooperative, Inc. and the Milton R. Young Station of Local Union 1593, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers: December 1, 1990 through November 30, 1993, Publication (Box 531, Folder 1)
- IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), Publication (Box 531, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Agreement between Local 827 International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO and New Jersey Bell Telephone Company: Pland and Engineering Departments: Effective August 6, 1989, Publication (Box 531, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Agreement between New England Telephone and Telegraph Company NYNEX Service Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (AFL-CIO) Locals 2222, 2313, 2320, 2321, 2322, 2323, 2324, 2325, 2326, 2327: effective: November 19, 1989, Publication (Box 531, Folder 2)
- IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), Publication (Box 531, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Agreement between System Council U-7 of the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, consisting of Local Unions 249, 945, 951, 961, 966, 992, 994, 1111, 1125, 1126 and 1143 and New York State Electric & Gas Corporation: effective July 1, 1991 thro, 1994; Publication (Box 531, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Agreement between Niagara Mohawk Power Corporation and System Council, U-11, and Local Unions 1339, 1352 (Western Division), 79, 310, 478, 554, 836, 1484 (Central Division), and 137, 1369, 1371, and 1385 (Eastern Division), International Brotherhood of El, 1986; Publication (Box 531, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Agreement between AG Communication Systems Corporation Northlake, Illinois and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 134: b 1191 Union contract, 1991; Publication (Box 531, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Agreement between New England Telephone Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (A.F.L.-C.I.O.), Locals 2222, 2320, 2323, 2324, 2327: effective August 10, 1980, Publication (Box 531, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Agreement between New England Telephone Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (A.F.L.-C.I.O.), Locals 2222, 2320, 2323, 2324, 2327: effective August 10, 1980, Publication (Box 531, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Agreement International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 569 and National Steel and Shipbuilding Company: October 1, 1984-September 30, 1987, Publication (Box 531, Folder 3)
- IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), Publication (Box 531, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Agreement between System Council U-7 of the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, consisting of Local Unions 249, 945, 951, 961, 966, 992, 994, 1111, 1125, 1126 and 1143 and New York State Electric & Gas Corporation: effective July 1, 1991 thro, 1991-1994 (Box 531, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Agreement between Local 827 International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO and New Jersey Bell Telephone Company: organization of Vice President and Comptroller and General Departments: Effective August 9, 1992, Publication (Box 531, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Agreement between NYNEX Materiel Enterprises Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO Locals 2222, 2313, 2320, 2321, 2322, 2323, 2324, 2325, 2326, 2327: effective November 19, 1989, Publication (Box 531, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Agreement between NYNEX Information Resources Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 2213: effective: November 19, 1989, Publication (Box 531, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Agreement between NYNEX Information Resources Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 2213: effective: September 1, 1991, Publication (Box 531, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Agreement between New England Telephone and Telegraph Company NYNEX Service Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (AFL-CIO) Locals 2222, 2313, 2320, 2321, 2322, 2323, 2324, 2325, 2326, 2327: effective: November 19, 1989, Publication (Box 531, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Agreement between New England Telephone and Telegraph Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO Locals 2222, 2313, 2320, 2321, 2322, 2323, 2324, 2325, 2326, 2327: effective: August 7, 1983, Publication (Box 531, Folder 4)
- IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), Publication (Box 532, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Extraordinary Medical Expense Agreement, 1969; Publication (Box 532, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Agreement between Western Electric Company Incorporated, Allentown Works, Allentown, Pa. and Local Union no. 1522, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, A.F.L.-C.I.O.: effective date, August 7, 1977, Publication (Box 532, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Agreement between Western Electric Company Incorporated, Allentown Works, Allentown, Pa. and Local Union no. 1522, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, A.F.L.-C.I.O.: effective date, July 18, 1969, Publication (Box 532, Folder 1)
- IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), Publication (Box 532, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Agreement between Telesector Resources Group and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Locals 2222, 2313, 2320, 2321, 2322, 2323, 2324, 2325, 2326, 2327: effective September 12, 1991, Publication (Box 532, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Agreement Zenith Radio Corporation, Rauland Division and Local 1031, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers affiliated with AFL-CIO: effective April 8, 1975, Publication (Box 532, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Agreement between Toshiba Display Devices Inc. and Local 1632, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1995; Publication (Box 532, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Agreement between Toshiba Display Devices Inc. and Local 1632, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1992; Publication (Box 532, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Agreement and pension and insurance agreement between Westinghouse Electric Corporation, and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (A.F.L.-C.I.O.): July 12, 1982, Publication (Box 532, Folder 2)
- IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), Publication (Box 532, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Notebook containing information on Job Security and Subcontracting Clauses which was sent to Joan Sickler, Vice Pres., Work in America Institute, Inc., 1992; Publication (Box 532, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Agreement and pension and insurance agreement between Westinghouse Electric Corporation and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (A.F.L.-C.I.O.): July 22, 1985, Publication (Box 532, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Agreement and pension and insurance agreement between Westinghouse Electric Corporation and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (A.F.L.-C.I.O.): August 29, 1988, Publication (Box 532, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Agreement and pension and insurance agreement between Westinghouse Electric Corporation and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (A.F.L.-C.I.O.): August 29, 1994, Publication (Box 532, Folder 3)
- IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), Publication (Box 532, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Amended Agreement -- copy of Amended agreement between the Company and Local Union 465 of IBEW, 1988; Publication (Box 532, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Report on the Proposed Collective Bargaining Agreement between the Staten Island Rapid Transit Operating Authority, 1978; Publication (Box 532, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Directory of Agreements, 1980-1982 (Box 532, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Contract between the Pacific Telephone and Telegraph Company and the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local Union 2139, Directory Sales Unit, Southern California, 1980; Publication (Box 532, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Agreement between Reidsville Plant of GTE Sylvania Incorporated and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 2290: December 1, 1976 to November 30, 1979, 1976-1979 (Box 532, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Agreement between the Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO: as amended August 10, 1980, Publication (Box 532, Folder 4)
- IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), Publication (Box 532, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Agreement between Ottawa Plant of GTE Sylvania and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO-CLC, Local 1654: b Sept. 24, 1976 to Sept. 24, 1979, 1976-1979 (Box 532, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Agreement between Pacific Gas and Electric Company and Local Union No. 1245 of International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, affiliated with American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations: applying to Operation, Maintenance and Const, 1980; Publication (Box 532, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Exhibit X., 1980; Publication (Box 532, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Exhibit X. Photo copy, 1991; Publication (Box 532, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Contract between the Pacific Telephone and Telegraph Company and the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local Union 2139, Directory Department Production Force, Southern California Region: effective August 10, 1980, Publication (Box 532, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Agreement between RCA Del Caribe, Inc. and Local Union 2333, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Barceloneta, Puerto Rico: February 17, 1978-February 20, 1981, 1978-1981 (Box 532, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Agreement between International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 1505, AFL-CIO and Raytheon Company: 1987-1989 (Box 532, Folder 5)
- IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), Publication (Box 533, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Local 3 IBEW 1989 Calendar, Publication (Box 533, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Union World, 1988; Publication (Box 533, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.49:no.7 (1988:July)
  - Item 3: Everybody joins unions, Publication (Box 533, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Composition of our brotherhood, 1988; Publication (Box 533, Folder 1)